[MUSIC]
As our world becomes increasingly digitized, so
does our ability to connect with it.
Imagine if you could search your surroundings the same way you
search the web.
Using existing cameras and advances in AI,
we can now find things and people in the real world,
in real time and take action to improve safety and well-being.
When a dangerous spill occurs in a chemical plant,
cameras recognize the incident.
Information about the spill is instantly shared with the people
who need it the most.
Enabling them to protect other employees from coming in contact
with the hazard,
[MUSIC]
And clean it up.
This technology can also help keep people safer in hospitals.
Patients recovering from heart surgery are limited to how much
they should exert themselves.
When someone exceeds the prescribed level of activity,
a nurse is alerted.
[MUSIC]
What&#39;s more,
the location of the closest wheelchair is identified, so
that the nurse can quickly get the patient seated and safe.
[MUSIC]
This technology is also useful in an environment like
a construction site.
Where people who need specialized tools are spread
out, sometimes across multiple floors.
Using cameras already in place,
this technology can identify a specific tool.
As well as the closest authorized person who
can deliver it.
Saving everyone time and keeping the workflow moving.
The digital and physical worlds are come together to help make
everyone more safe, secure, and productive.
And we&#39;re bringing the Edge of Microsoft&#39;s Cloud to any device.
[MUSIC]